digimindsoft.com 2013-05-23

# Digital Minds Software - Privacy Policy

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. We reserve the right to change this policy from time to time and will post the changes to our website. Please check it periodically to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of our website will signify your acceptance of these changes. 

## Personal Information

Any personal details that you provide to our website shall stay absolutely safe, private, and secure. We respect the importance of information security and confidentiality and do not disclose or resell it to outside sources. We will not share your information with any third parties except for verified secure e-commerce transaction providers. When placing an order, our e-commerce partner will handle your personal information and keep it absolutely safe and secure. They have their own privacy policy which is made available to you when you are referred to their site. In fact, even we cannot access your credit card information. Your personal information (excluding credit card data) is shared only with us for administration purposes. You can always choose not to provide your personal details, even though they might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of some of digimindsoft.com's specific features. 

## Information that We May Collect from Our Users

Digital Minds Software may collect personal information to improve the manner by which we operate and offer our products and services, communicate with you about those products and services, and provide effective, timely customer support when needed. We may collect the following information from our users but only if voluntarily provided to us: 

  * First name, last name, e-mail, billing address, phone number
  * For processing transactions, we also collect either credit card information or bank information, depending on your form of payment. We do not store any credit card information after your transaction is complete.

## Cookies

Our website may use cookies to store information about your visits and enhance your on-line experience. Cookies are small files downloaded to your computer to track movements within websites. Cookies link to information regarding what items you have selected for purchase at our store. This information is used to keep track of your shopping cart. Cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of this site's coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. We don't store any of your personal information in our cookies. 

## Email Newsletter

Our newsletter is strictly run as an "opt-out" newsletter. We never send unsolicited emails. Information gathered during voluntary newsletter subscription is restricted to email address. This information is used solely by Digital Minds Software and will not be sold to, or used by, any third party. Digital Minds Software will use this information only for sending the regular newsletter about product updates, new releases and special offers. If you do not want to receive newsletters or other mail from us, you can always unsubscribe from these at any time. In every email we send, you will find clear instructions how to do it. 

## Security

We have taken the appropriate steps and followed industry standards to secure any personal data stored by our systems. All transactions are processed by the highest security level protocols ensuring that no one can access or use personal information in an unauthorized manner. 

## Credit Card Transactions

We do not store any credit card information (name on credit card, credit card number and expiry date) for any purchase made on our site. 

## External Links

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

## Agreement with Digital Minds Software Policies

By using any of the Digital Minds Software websites, products, or services, you signify your understanding of and assent to the Digital Minds Software Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, we strongly urge that you do not use any of Digital Minds Software websites, products, or services. 

## Contact Us about Privacy

If, for any reason, you are concerned with the way that we may be using your personal information, you would like to request that we cease from using your personal information, or you wish to file a complaint, please Contact us. 

_Last modified: April 7, 2011_
